What's this smell?
What was that sound?
Where are you going?
No, I hate this.
It's crazy.
HARUTO!
JEONG WOO!
JUNG HWAN!
YOSHI!
HYUN SUK!
Where are you going?
I'm not kidding, I really can't do this.
I'm just too scared!
I'm alone.
Are all the TREASURE members here?
What?
Hey!
I don't want to take the blindfold off.
This is...
It's...
Huh?
JEONG WOO!
What?
Gosh, that scared me.
A phone?
What?
It's a phone.
Huh?
It has my name on it.
A meesage.
How do I do this?
From the basement to the fourth floor
find the two keys in each floor.
During the hide and seek, if you get caught
you can use the key to be freed again.
Two in each floor?
They've really prepared properly for this.
It's totally different to what we've done so far.
It's quite scary here.
I'll be quiet.
I'll go downstairs first.
Two in each floor?
I'm sorry.
It was you.
Let's turn this off.
I really can't do this.
Gosh, that scared me!
I thought about this before.
It could be something like
finding an item, like the Running Man.
Look, in here
you can tell
it's not somewhere I shouldn't go.
Right?
Look.
But there's no camera here.
Maybe I shouldn't go there.
Sorry.
Here.
Let's find a place to hide.
I need to check these places
because I might have to hide.
Let's start.
Start!
Find the two keys in each floor.
Hmm, keys.
There's none here.
I don't know what the keys look like.
ASAHI.
What, are you caught?
No.
ASAHI, do you have the keys?
No, I'm still looking for them.
Right.
I'll go and find them!
Okay.
I'll look for them.
Why is there
a plastic bag?
Finding the keys is a good thing.
And it's even better if I know which floor I'm on.
I shouldn't be looking like this.
They'll tease me again.
Huh?
Hello?
Who are you?
Are you Choi HYUN SUK?
You are...
I'm actually JUNKYU.
What?
Are you locked in a jail?
No.
Are you in a jail?
Yes, I'm locked in a jail.
If you find a key, can you let me out?
I think I just found some keys.
But I'm not sure if these are real
so I'll check and and let you know.
Okay.
It was JUNKYU.
How did he know my number though?
How does he know my number?
Phone book.
How did he know my number?
There's Choi HYUN SUK's number and YOSHI's number.
JEONG WOO.
Yes, JUNG HWAN.
Be quiet.
Do we have to stay quiet?
I don't know, just be quiet.
Don't you think there might be some items?
No, I don't think so.
I'm looking for them.
It's a walkie-talkie.
Hey!
JUNGHWAN, grab a walkie-talkie.
Okay.
What was that sound?
Hey.
How do I use the walkie-talkie?
Turn it on.
Is that JEONG WOO?
You scared me.
We found a walkie-talkie.
What?
Can we go out?
Yes, there's something.
Come out, hurry.
Let's check the third floor first.
Are we going?
Yes.
There was a photo.
A photo?
A photo of a baby.
Two in each floor?
I'm scared, I can't find them on my own.
I'm scared.
What do they look like?
YOSHI!
You're not it, are you?
I'm not.
- Two on each floor.
- Let's find the keys.
Ah, there are two on each floor?
Yes.
Do you want to stay with me? I'm a little scared.
Let's stay together.
Let's stay together for now.
Okay.
If we find the key
the one who find it gets to keep it.
I found something that look like keys.
But I'm not sure if this is the one.
How do I go past here?
I can't see anything.
But...
How do I do this?
How can they
expect someone to do this?
I found the keys.
Where?
There are several.
Those might not be it.
That phone bell is scary, right?
Yes, it really is!
Let's stay together.
Okay, I'm scared.
Hey!
Yes.
JIHOON?
Yes, come up.
JAE HYUK.
What are you doing?
Hey!
What's that?
Huh?
A nightstick.
Why? Are you a spy?
No, it's just a weapon.
You scared me.
JAE HYUK, come here.
I think it's better if we stay together.
I was alone on the fourth floor and got really scared.
Are we on the fourth floor?
No, this is the third floor.
Have you searched everywhere?
Yes, I've searched everywhere.
Where's the key?
It was in that room.
JEONG WOO.
There's another door over the window.
Did you see it?
I didn't look there.
Huh?
JAE HYUK.
HARUTO.
HARUTO!
JAE HYUK.
HARUTO.
Yes.
- Come.
- Where?
Come here.
Who do you think will fall for that?
HARUTO, quick.
No.
Don't come, then!
I'm scared.
The smog, gosh.
HARUTO.
Please trust me, just once.
I bet our friendship.
I want to go in here.
I want to go in but I can't.
There's a walkie-talkie there.
Someone come with me.
You have to film me anyway, so can you come with me?
No?
JEONG WOO!
Huh?
Come over here.
Why?
- There's a suspicious room here.
- Where are you?
Where are you?
He's acting strange.
JEONG WOO, I bet our friendship on this, please!
Where are you?
Here.
Why?
There's a walkie-talkie in there.
I want to go in
but there's too much smog.
Look, you know what I mean?
There are boxes and stuff.
I think it's the same walkie-talkie.
This one, right?
Can we connect with walkie-talkies?
We need to take that, then.
There's something in here.
Why is there smog in this room?
I know.
Let's go in.
Can you go first?
You're the oldest here.
There are stairs.
You only call me hyung at times like this.
There are stairs, I'm scared.
There are boxes and stuff in here.
There are stairs so be careful when you run away.
Right.
I think there's something on the floor.
I'm sure, for definite.
Why else would they have so much smog in here?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Wait, here.
What?
What did you do?
That opened.
Calm down.
It could have just opened because of the wind.
I'm really scared.
There must be something here.
None?
No.
There should be something.
No, I looked everywhere.
Hey!
Nice.
We didn't go in here.
It's too scary here.
This place shouldn't be it.
But there's a camera there, so there must be something.
I think.
Right?
Is there a key?
Huh?
You found the key?
Is that it?
We need to find a key?
Isn't this the key?
Did they say we need to find a key?
Yes.
Who?
We received a mail.
- The text.
- The phone.
There's a phone?
Hey, I found one.
This is it.
Right, nice one.
I'll go and save JUNKYU.
Okay.
Help me out!
JUNKYU.
Yes!
He's here.
Help me!
- Hello.
Hey.
We need to call the gatekeeper.
Huh?
The gatekeeper.
Did you start from there?
What?
Why did you start from here?
I don't know, I was spawned here.
What?
But there's some sort of numbers here.
But what does that 4,444 seconds mean?
4,444.
What does that mean?
Oh my god!
Look behind!
Why are they here?
Exactly.
Gosh, you scared me.
Why did you bring that?
I thought you were it.
There's someone in here.
I was so scared.
No one saved them.
Look over there.
They're in here.
I think they'll be released.
We should be hiding then.
JEONG WOO, let's go to the fourth floor.
Okay.
Fourth floor?
It's small.
I'm coming from the fourth floor.
There was nothing there.
It's here.
It's here, but it's faster when one person seeks out and two search.
But I really can't go there, I'm sorry.
I'm too scared.
It really is scary.
But there's nothing.
Let's go in.
Let's search.
I was here.
You were here?
Yes.
Really
scared.
I think it's downstairs.
I don't think it's on the fourth floor.
They said there are two on each floor.
We need to find the keys.
How do I hide later?
No electricity.
Something should be in here.
Anyone wants to light up here?
Nothing.
Do we have to open up all the boxes?
Have you looked in here?
We should have gone to that hidden room before.
- Do you want to go?
- The smog room.
Do you want to go?
I'll go.
Let's go.
Hey.
- They're not even scared?
- What?
What?
We did find that walkie-talkie before.
Let's open the boxes.
Yes, let's open the boxes.
Someone here was...
You found it?
I'm it now.
Can you hide well?
Good luck.
Hide and seek
Wherever you are
Here I come
Hide and seek
I see JUNKYU
I see ASAHI